Penny?
[KNOCKING]
PENNY:
Sheldon?
- Penny?
[KNOCKING] Sheldon?
(Scene:)- Penny.
[KNOCKING] Sheldon.
Penny!
- What do you want?
- I need access...
(Sheldon:)...to the Cheesecake Factory's
walk-in freezer.
(Penny:)Honey, I already told you...
(Penny:)...the hamburger meat is fresh
and stored at a safe temperature.
(Sheldon:)No, this is to train for a three-month
expedition to the magnetic north pole.
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)I don't know how that sentence
could possibly confuse you...
(Sheldon:)...but to elaborate,
I am going to the Arctic Circle...
(Sheldon:)...with Leonard, Wolowitz,
and Koothrappali.
- You're all going?
- Yes.
- For three months?
(Penny:)Excuse me.
Wait, is that a yes or a no
on the freezer?